Bradley Levick

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

CAREER OBJECTIVES

Playtesting

OA Testing

Localisation

Problem Solving

Reporting Bugs

Bug Fixing

Industry Knowledge

Working In A Team

Working Independently

Communication Skills

Unity

Unreal Engine

Game Maker Studio

Coding

Photoshop

Maya

Microsoft Office

IT skills

Team Leading

Recruitment

People Management

Staff Training

Documented Meetings Marketing Campaigns

Event Organisation

PROFESSIONAL

Administration

From a young age I have enjoyed creating custom game content, from designing levels to creating my own games from scratch. It is my ambition to transition my passion and subsequent education into a full time career working in the games industry. Over recent years I have worked with various BAFTA award winning companies. I continue to push myself towards acquiring a full time position in QA.

Developing games has long been my goal and motivation. I relish the opportunity to learn new skills and techniques and I am confident I could become a valuable asset to your team.

EXPERIENCE

December 2015

ID SOFTWARE, REMOTE

DOOM (XBOX ONE) - CLOSED ALPHA TESTER

October 2015

BITHELL GAMES, LONDON VOLUME: CODA (PS4) – PLAYTESTER

February 2015

ROLL7, LONDON

NOT A HERO (STEAM) - PLAYTESTER

November 2014 - December 2014

PLUG-IN MEDIA, BRIGHTON QA LOCALISATION – WORK EXPERIENCE

- Worked on QA Localization (Dora & Friends IOS App) Project Management / task tracking (Trello)
- SVN version control
- Debugging processes
- Experience working in a professional AGILE environment
- Attended production meetings
- Knowledge and understanding of the development process
- Professional training with Unity
- Worked with web tools, languages and syntaxes HTML5 / JavaScript / CSS / XML
- Phaser game framework, Grunt, Node.js, JSON

September 2014 – November 2014

VMC (ON BEHALF OF UBISOFT) THE CREW (PS4) – CLOSED BETA TESTER

August 2014 – September 2014

TEAM17 DIGITAL, WEST YORKSHIRE

PENARIUM (STEAM) - PLAYTESTER

FUTURLAB, BRIGHTON VELOCITY 2X (PS4) - PLAYTESTER

QUALIFICATIONS

'Take Control' Assistant Manager Training

'Take Control' Store Manager Training

OTHER EXPERIENCE

January 2017 – Present

PRESS START 2 JOIN, VARIOUS LOCATIONS

FREELANCE EVENTS ORGANISER / TEAM LEADER

November 2017 – April 2018

HOBISTAR, ONLINE RETAILER

SOLE PROPRIETOR

December 2016 - April 2017

CEX, EAST GRINSTEAD

STORE MANAGER

July 2013 – April 2014

ODDBALLS INTERNATIONAL, SOUTHWICK

WEBSITE DESIGNER / ADMINISTRATOR

June 2011 - July 2013

BLOCKBUSTER GAMES, BURGESS HILL/EASTBOURNE

RETAIL GAMES MANAGER / FLAGSHIP STORE MANAGER

October 2009 - July 2011

GAMESTATION, BANGOR

SALES ASSISTANT

March 2008 – September 2009

BLOCKBUSTER, HAYWARDS HEATH/BURGESS HILL

MANAGER ON DUTY/SHIFT RUNNER

February 2007 - August 2007

CHOICES UK, HAYWARDS HEATH

SUPERVISOR

EDUCATION

07/09/09 - 24/06/11

COLEG MENAI, LLANGEFNI

NATIONAL DIPLOMA INTERACTIVE MEDIA

Awarded Triple Distinction overall grade, achieving distinction level in all 48 assignment modules

09/1998 - 07/2003

OATHALL COMMUNITY COLLEGE, WEST SUSSEX

 $\label{eq:GCSE: Science Double Award (C,C), Mathematics (B), English Literature (C), English Language (C), French (C), Design Technology Electronics (C), Art & Design (B), Physical Education (C)$

REFEREES

Personal Details

Bradley Michael Levick

112 Parklands Road Hassocks West Sussex BN6 8LF

(T) 07456 299 092

(E) Bradlevick@hotmail.co.uk

(W) www.brad-levick.squarespace.com

Dean Hedger

Owner/End Level Boss, PressStart2Join

Pressstart2join@outlook.com

Alan Owen

Technical Director, Plug-In Media alan.owen@pluginmedia.net

Steve Gorst

Head of Games Development team, Coleg Menai

gorst1s@gllm.ac.uk

Additional references can be provided upon request